A Guide to the Maps and flat files FA465
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Harold P. Fabian, 43
  - "JY Ranch Projects, 1960." Series of 7 blueprints of site plan and cabin outlines., 1960 August-September; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 7). Oversized. (Drawer C 4, Folder 2)
  - "JY Ranch Projects, 1960: Site Plan & Project Outline.", 1960 August 11; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 4, Folder 2)
  - Plot Plan of JY Ranch Showing Underground Utilities., 1961 September 1; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 4, Folder 2)
- Charles Burton Fahs, 44
  - Certificate for the order of the Sacred Treasure, 3rd Class from Emperor of Japan, with translation, 1960 July 12; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 4, Folder 7)
- Lawrence B. Dunham, 45
  - schematic drawing of "Auxilary Cutter Yacht for Mr. L.B. Dunham-Form Draught" (Laurent, Giles & Partners, England), 1930 July 21; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 13, Folder 1)
  - general construction plan for "Proposed Auxilary Yacht for Mr. L.B. Dunham-Form Draught" (Laurent, Giles & Partners, England), 1930 March 4; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 13, Folder 1)
  - schematics for "Auxilary Yawl for Mr. Dunham" design #146, boat is called "Vrayling II" (Sparkman & Stevens Inc.), 1936; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 10) (Drawer E 13, Folder 1)
  - schematic drawing for "Design #85-26" (part of boat) (Sparkman & Stevens Inc.), 1937 February; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 13, Folder 1)
- Paul Ehrlich, 46
  - "Selective Toxicity: A Legacy of Paul Ehrlich" poster for lecture by Ernest Bueding at Johns Hopkins University, 1981 April 22; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer J 1, Folder 4)
- Lewis W. Hackett, 47
  - Sketch Map of India, Burma, and Ceylon. Lithograph., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 1, Folder 7)
  - Lithograph of Ceylon indicating railways and roads., MAP (Quantity 1); On tissue paper. (Drawer C 1, Folder 7)
  - "Map of United Provinces." Indicates Malaria distribution in India (color)., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 1, Folder 7)
  - "Per La Difesa Dalla Malaria." Public ordinance issued by the municipal government of Rome., 1931 March 12; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 1, Folder 7)
  - Map of Albania, hand-drawn by Italian cartographer Giacomo Cantelli da Vignola., 1689; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 1, Folder 7)
  - China Population Distributions (regarding 1945).", 1957; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 1, Folder 7)
- John H. Knowles, 48
  - Honorary degree to John Hilton Knowles: Doctor of Humane Letters, awarded by Boston University., AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
  - "Why Shouldn't Blue Cross Pay Taxes?", 1964 May 15; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
    removed from Series 2, Subseries 1, box 13, folders 150-154: reimbursements fro in-house patients
  - Series of 4 blueprints for the office of Dr. John H. Knowles., 1972 August-September; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
    Removed from box 84, folder 988
  - Series of 3 blueprint negatives for the proposed addition to the Vincent Burnum Building of the Massachusetts General Hospital., 1961 January 6; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
    removed from box 9, folder 96
  - Proposed alterations nursery fourth floor," Vincent Burnum Building, Massachusetts General Hospital., 1962 February 5; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
    removed from box 12, folder 143
  - Series of 2 whiteprints for the Mosley Building of the Massachusetts General Hospital., 1962; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
  - "Proposed alterations for psychiatric service," Bulfinch Building Mass.General Hospital, 1967 May 12; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
  - "Alterations to conference room," Vincent Burnum Building, Mass. General Hospital, 1965 April 13; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
  - Honorary degree: Doctor of Law, awarded by Suffolk University, 1975 June 8; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
    removed from Box 114
  - certificate of election as a Fellow of the New York Academy of Medicine, 1947 January 6; AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
  - certificate of membership of the Medical Assistance Advisory Council, from the Commonwealth of Massachusetts (certificate and small program), 1966 December 13; AWARD (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
  - honorary degree: Doctor of Science from the New York Medical College, 1975 June 3; AWARD (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
  - license to practice medicine and surgery in New York State, 1972 May 15; AWARD (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
  - Award, AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
  - Award, AWARD (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 11, Folder 1)
- Leopold Koss, 49
  - Honorary Degree Conferred upon Leopold Koss form the Severance Union Medical College., 1956 November 24; CITATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer J 1, Folder 7)
    Accession 2012:079.
    Separated from Koss papers. No specific separation information accompanies the citation.
- William M. Myers, 50
  - Map of West Africa. Printed at the survey of Ghana at Accra., 1959; MAP (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer C 1, Folder 8)
    M-2
  - Road Map of Nigeria., 1960; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 1, Folder 8)
- Leonard Outhwaite, 51
  - Proposed Oceangoing raft, overall length 100 ft., 1964 October 2; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 2, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Oceangoing Raft: Golfstreamer, 125 ft. boat, 1964 November 12; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 2, Folder 2)
  - Design # 793, 97 ft., three-masted sailing yacht, general arrangement. Yacht schematic indicating levels., 1967 September-December; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer C 2, Folder 2)
  - 97 and 1/2 foot three masted sailing yacht, outboard profile, part of the gulfstream project., 1967 June-December; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer C 2, Folder 2)
  - Design #C-793: 97 and 1/2 foot three masted sailing yacht, preliminary sail plan, 1967 June-December; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 2, Folder 2)
- Oscar M. Ruebhausen, 52
  - 2 certificates and a decree appointing Ruebhausen to the General Advisory Committee on Atomic Energy for New York State, signed by NAR, 1959, 1961; AWARD (Quantity 3) (Drawer N 9, Folder 1)
    Former Classification: IV 3A 28.
- Benjamin E. Washburn, 53
  - "Notice: Latrines Must Be Used." Poster by local health board., 1920 July `; POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 2, Folder 5)
    Former Classification: IVA13.3.
    Separated from: Box 3, Folder 31
  - "Who Will Solve This Problem?" The State Journal: A Weekly Mirror of North Carolina Life. Newspaper clipping (double-sided)., 1916 February 4; PUBLICATION (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 2, Folder 5)
    Separated from: Box 7, Folder 57
  - "Notice! To the Citizens of Wilson: Annual Spring Cleanup." Poster soliciting cooperation for community cleanup., POSTER (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 2, Folder 5)
    Separated from: Box 5, Folder 46
  - Map of the Island of Jamaica. Prepared for the Jamaica handbook., 1895; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer C 2, Folder 5)
    Separated from: Box 1, Folder 24
- Joseph Willits, 54
  - Proposed Alterations to Whippoorwill School., 1961 February 16; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer C 2, Folder 6)
- John D. Rockefeller 3rd Associates: Edgar B. Young, 55
  - Scan of Lincoln Center Floor plan., 1961 April; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 1)
    Separated from Series 1.2 Art, Box 11, Folder 115
  - 2 copies of floor plan for Calder sculpture, with letter., 1965 June; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer D 14, Folder 1)
    Separated from Series 1.2 Art, Box 13, Folder 138
  - Correspondence and Floor plan for Opera Tower, Rockefeller Center., 1960 December; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 1)
    Separated from Series 1.3 Bldg. Ops., Box 15, Folder 167
  - Floor plan for Sculptures at Julliard School of Music., 1968 January 18; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 1)
    Separated from Series 1.2 Art, Box 12, Folder 120
  - Lincoln Center Site Plan., 1959 July 16; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 2)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 42, Folder 525
  - Lincoln Center "Plaza Level 1" Layout., 1958 July 22; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 2)
  - Lincoln Center Site Plan., 1959 August 6; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 2)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 42, Folder 522
  - Proposed Time Schedule for Metropolitan Opera. Lincoln Center., 1960 January 26; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 2)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 40, Folder 484
  - "Preliminary Japan House Indoor Garden." 21-page Booklet of Architectural drawings by Junzo Yoshimura. For Japan Society., 1968 July 10; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 21) (Drawer D 14, Folder 2)
  - Lincoln Center "Plaza Level 1" Layout., 1958 July 22; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 3)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 43, Folder 526
  - Lincoln Center Site Plan., 1959 August 6; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 3)
  - Plan for Lincoln Center Plaza Upper Level Plan. With Correspondence., 1961 February; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 3)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 43, Folder 535
  - Plan of Lincoln Center Property. With Financial Report attached., 1959 September; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 3)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 43, Folder 532
  - Photocopy of Garage Plan at Lincoln Center. "Enclosure 3A.", 1959 September; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1); oversized and folded. (Drawer D 14, Folder 3)
  - Photocopy of Plan for Lincoln Center Plaza Lower Level Plan. With Correspondence., 1961 February; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 3)
  - photocopy of Julliard School of Music site plan, with correspondence, 1964 May 8; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 4)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 44, Folder 559
  - photocopy of Julliard School of Music site plan, with correspondence, 1964 May 8; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 4)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 45, Folder 560
  - photocopy of Amsterdam Tower plan, Julliard School of Music, with correspondence, 1964 June 1; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 4)
  - photocopy of Julliard School of Music floor plans, with correspondence, 1964 June 1; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 4)
  - photocopy of street plan of Julliard Building, Lincoln Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project, 1965 April 15; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 5)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 46, Folder 576
  - set of 6 drawings "Feasibility Study for Lincoln Center of Proposed Multi-Use Building... " Schemes 1-4B, 1974 December-1968; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 6) (Drawer D 14, Folder 5)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 47, Folder 584
  - photocopy of site and street plans of Lincoln Center, w/ correspondence, 1958 January-February; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 5)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction, Box 48, Folder 603
  - map of "Lincoln Square Area" from Lincoln-Amsterdam Urban Renewal Project General Files, 1965 April 15; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 5)
  - Julliard School of Music site plan for green space, photocopy w/ correspondence, 1967-1970; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 5)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 48, Folder 600
  - Julliard Building site expansion, 1958 January-February; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 5)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 48, Folder 603
  - Comparison of March 1959 Plan with September 1959 Plan-Philharmonic Plan, Lincoln Center, with correspondence, 1959 October 28; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 6)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 56, Folder 715
  - Philharmonic Hall Acoustics Study, Lincoln Center w/ correspondence, WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 6)
  - Lincoln Center site, photocopy w/correspondence, 1955 March; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 6)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 54, Folder 691
  - Re-Development of Lincoln Center Square Park, photocopy w/ correspondence, 1960 May 5; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 6)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 54, Folder 688
  - Study for Development of Triangular Park Area, photocopy, w/ correspondence, 1964 November-1965 September; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 6)
  - Existing Condition of Broadway Malls, with correspondence., 1964 November-1965 September; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 6)
  - Repertory Theatre for Drama & Library Museum, Lincoln Center, 1964 January 6; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 9) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning & Construction Box 49, Folder 624
  - Preliminary Plans and Schematic Elevations, Lincoln Square Plaza, 1960 March 21; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
    Separated from Series 1.10 Public Relations Box 64, Folder 827
  - Lincoln Center neighborhood, 1958 March-1961 August; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
  - Philharmonic Hall, Lincoln Center, 1959 May 9; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning and Construction, Box 58, Folder 751
  - Philharmonic Hall: Plaza Level, Scheme B6, 1960 April-1961 June; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning and Construction, Box 57, Folder 735
  - Philharmonic Hall: Plaza Level, Scheme A5, 1960 April-1961 June; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
  - Family of Halls with Similar Ceiling Shapes, 1962 November-1963 June; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning and Construction, Box 56, Folder 716
  - Family of Halls, comparisons, 1962 November-1963 June; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning and Construction, Box 56, Folder 715
  - comparison of Philharmonic, Carnegie, Boston, and Grosser music halls, 1962 November-1963 June; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer D 14, Folder 7)
  - Booklet "Feasibility Study for U.D.C." Lincoln Center, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 14) (Drawer D 14, Folder 8)
    Separated from Series 1.9 Planning and Construction, Box 60, Folder 765
- Hudson Highlands, 56
  - Conservation Resources Group: The Hudson Highlands. 4 sheets, 2 labeled "Active Projects"., undated; MAPS (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
  - Hudson Highlands (2 copies), MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - 2 different U.S.G.S. maps of Hudson Valley w/ land proposals noted in pen & glue-on labels, 1957; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - Cold Spring region-Hudson Highlands Project, 1985 March; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - Hudson Valley w/ colored land plats denoting parks, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - Hudson Highlands project area, with park areas highlighted, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous, 57
  - 2 schematics (plate 33, 34) of Building Zone Restrictions--Part of Section 5, from 42nd to 47nd S, between FDR and 3rd Ave in Manhattan, ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 14, Folder 1)
  - Topographic survey of property of W.K. Harrison, West Hills, Town of Huntington, Suffolk County, NY; drawn in pencil with some pen notations, 1955 August 8; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 14, Folder 1)
  - Proposed move of the Tin House by W.K. Harrison; pencil drawings on vellum (Wallace K. Harrison), 1955 August 8; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 14, Folder 1)
  - painting of stone building with Asian decorative elements, marked "Proposed building", RENDERING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 14, Folder 2)
    "P-MS P34x no. 2"
  - packet of plans "Lindisfarne Hermitage at the Cathedral of St. John the Divine, NY NY" (John Barton, architect), 1992 May 5; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 6) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - Museum of Modern Art (MOMA): plot plan, 1968 May 1; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
    marked "L.L. L.Peters"
  - surveys of area around Harlem River, at Seekonk Realty Corp, on a range of materials, 1965; MAP (Quantity 6) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - set of surveys of St. John, U.S. Virgin Islands (US Dept of Interior, Land Resources Department), 1983 June; MAP (Quantity 12) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - set of surveys Virgin Island National Park (US Dept of Interior, Land Resources Dept), 1974 May; MAP (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - USGS maps of St. John's Island, US Virgin Islands, 1982; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - colored maps of the Virgin Islands, 1973 November 13; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - blueline of dedication plaque for JDR Jr. Parkway in Wyoming (Dale B. Thompson), 1975 August 8; RENDERING (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - colored land survey of Grand Teton National Park, "Land Donations & Withdrawals" (Dept of Interior, National Park Service), 1969 September; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - map "Traffic Flow, State of Wyoming" (Wyoming Highway Department), 1975; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - USGS map of Acme, Wyoming w/ different notes, 1978; MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)